rogerebert.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Roger Ebert

### This Privacy Policy applies to our sites and apps

Ebert Digital LLC’s “hereinafter Ebert Digital” Privacy Policy is designed to inform users about the type of information we collect, and how we collect, use and safeguard the information we collect on our Website. By using our website and app, you consent to our Privacy Policy. 

This policy was last updated on May 28, 2013.

  * Update Policy
  * Terms and Conditions
  * The Type of Information We Collect
  * Consent to Collect Information
  * We May Share Information With Third Party Service Providers
  * Compliance with Law and Fraud Protection
  * You must be 18 to order from this website
  * Third Party Links
  * Right to Transfer Personal Information
  * Right to Opt Out
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * U.S. Laws
  * Contacting Us

#### Update Policy

Ebert Digital will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When a revision is made we will revise the “last updated” date on this page and post a link to the revisions. We encourage you to check the date of our Privacy Policy each time you visit our Website for any updates or changes. Your use of our Website constitutes your consent to this Privacy Policy, including any changes or updates.

↑ Back to top

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers and limitations governing the use of our website.

↑ Back to top

#### The Type of Information We Collect

If you request any information from us you will be required to provide your name, email address and telephone number.

**Contact Information.** The type of Information we collect depends upon the services you use and/or products you purchase. This information will be stored so we may provide you with service and use to contact you.

**Payment Information.** If you purchase one of our products or services, we will collect your credit card information, shipping address, billing address, e-mail address, telephone number, and purchase information.

**Information You Post or Submit.** We collect and store information you post or submit on our website.

**Newsletters.** Ebert Digital offers newsletters. If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name, street address and e-mail address to provide these communications. We respect your privacy, so we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see opt-out section below.

**Surveys & Sweepstakes.** Ebert Digital may offer special events such as surveys or sweepstakes. In order to participate in any such surveys or sweepstakes we will request additional information from our customers that may include contact information (such as name, shipping address and e-mail address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Browsing our Website - Usage Tracking.** Ebert Digital’s database tracks the traffic throughout our site. This information is used to compile overall statistics and is not recorded at an individual level. This includes IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate. The statistics help us decide which products and services best serve our members and guests.

**Cookies and Web Beacons.** In some instances, Ebert Digital may collect data through cookies, web logs, web beacons (also known as pixel gifs or action tags) and other monitoring technologies to enhance your browsing and shopping experience on our website. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive to collect information about your activities on our website. Web beacons are small strings of code placed on a web page or within an email for the purpose of transferring information.

We use cookies and web beacons to deliver our ads, improve and measure the usability, track visits from our affiliates and partners, performance and effectiveness of our Website, improve and measure the effectiveness of our marketing programs, learn how customers use our website, estimate our audience size, deliver co-branded services, and to customize your shopping experience. Examples of the type of information that we collect through these collection devices, includes: total visitors to the website, pages viewed, unique visitors, time spent on our Website and on certain web pages, etc.

We may authorize third parties to use cookies, web beacons and other monitoring technologies to compile information about the use of the Website or interaction with advertisements that appear on the Website. You are always free to decline cookies if your browser permits, although, by declining the use of cookies you may not be able to use certain features on the Website.

↑ Back to top

#### Consent to Collect Information

When you submit your personal information to us, you are giving us your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We are always available to discuss your questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices. If you would like to speak to a customer service representative, please contact us via telephone at (312) 450-6324 or e-mail us at [webmaster@ebertdigital.com](mailto:webmaster@ebertdigital.com).

↑ Back to top

#### We May Share Information With Third Party Service Providers:

We use trusted third-party service providers to perform certain services on our behalf, including: shipping, payment processing, data storage/management, webhosting, web analytics, fulfillment, marketing, mailing, emailing, etc. These service providers only receive personal information if such information is needed to perform their function(s), and they are not authorized to use any personal information for any other purpose(s) other than the purpose(s) set forth by Ebert Digital.

↑ Back to top

#### Compliance with Law and Fraud Protection

We may, and you authorize us to use and disclose any information, including personal information: (1) we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; (2) in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any personal or as otherwise required by law; (3) to other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction; and (4) to enforce any agreement we have with you.

↑ Back to top

#### You must be 18 to order from this website

Ebert Digital does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18. If we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 18, we will delete that data from our systems. Please visit the FTC’s website at [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/) for tips on protecting children’s privacy online.

↑ Back to top

#### Third Party Links

Our Website may provide links to other third-party Websites which are outside our control and not covered by this privacy policy. This may include our name because we may partner with the third-party. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) Websites.

↑ Back to top

#### Right to Transfer Personal Information

Your personally identifiable information may be disclosed to a third party as part of a merger, sale of the company assets or acquisition, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, in which personally identifiable information would be transferred as one of the business assets of Ebert Digital.

↑ Back to top

#### Right to Opt Out

We want to communicate with you only if you want to continue to hear from us.

To opt out of receiving email promotions that we send you: (1) select “unsubscribe” on our subscription status page and enter the requested information or follow the unsubscribe instructions in any of our promotional emails. To opt out of telephone promotions, you can tell us when we call you.

Opting out of communication with us does not affect our communications with you via telephone or email related to your orders with us. It also does not affect our use of your non-personally identifiable information.

↑ Back to top

#### Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident and would like a copy of our notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for their direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of the third parties and affiliates that received your information in the past year, please submit a request to [webmaster@ebertdigital.com](mailto:webmaster@ebertdigital.com).

↑ Back to top

#### U.S. Laws

You understand that all information is stored in the United States and is subject to the laws of the United States.

↑ Back to top

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may e-mail us at [webmaster@ebertdigital.com](mailto:webmaster@ebertdigital.com) or contact us at (312) 450-6324.

↑ Back to top
